现在我们来谈谈自动化测试和回归测试。
Now let's talk about automated testing and regression testing.
事实上，这两者的结合，
And in fact, the combination of those two,
自动回归测试
automated regression testing, which
是现代软件工程的最佳实践之一。
is one of the best practices in modern software engineering.
没有什么能让测试更容易运行，
Nothing makes tests easier to run,
对一般程序员来说
and more likely for the average programmer
运行它们，然后让测试完全自动化。
to run them, then having the test be completely automated.
这意味着你只要按下一个按钮，测试就会运行，
It means that you can just push a button, the test will run,
他们会自动检查自己的结果。
and they'll check their own results automatically.
测试不应是交互式程序
The test should not be an interactive program
它会提示您输入并打印出结果
that prompts you for its inputs and prints out its results
你可以用你的眼球手动检查。
for you to manually check with your eyeballs.
相反，它应该做的是运行模块，运行
Instead what it should do is run the module, run
方法本身，使用这些选定的固定测试用例
the method itself, using these fixed test cases selected
我们在这篇文章中谈到的，
in the ways that we've talked about in this reading,
然后自动检查结果是否正确。
and then automatically check that the results are correct.
然后所有测试套件的结果
And then the result of all of the test suite
应该是，嘿，所有的测试都可以。
should be either, hey, all tests are OK.
或者，看，下面的测试失败了
Or, look, the following tests failed
你应该去调查他们。
and you should go and investigate them.
它们有多种语言，包括Java。
They're in many languages, including Java.
很好的测试框架，使之更容易
Great testing frameworks that make it easy
为您编写这些类型的测试驱动程序。
for you to write these kinds of test drivers.
我们在这个类中使用的是JUnit。
The one that we're using in this class is JUnit.
现在像JUnit这样的自动化测试框架
Now automated testing frameworks like JUnit
使运行测试变得容易，但您仍然
make easy to run the tests, but you still
必须自己提出测试用例。
have to come up with the test cases yourself.
总有一天我们会自动生成测试，
Someday we'll have automatic test generation,
但这仍然是个难题
but it's still a hard problem and still
一种主观的、积极的计算机科学研究。
a subjective, active computer science research.
所以我们在这里讨论的那种自动化测试
So the kind of automated testing we're talking about here
只是在创建测试后运行测试。
is just running the tests once you've created them.
一旦你有了测试自动化
Now once you have a test automation
你应该尽可能频繁地运行它。
you should run it as frequently as you can get away with.
重新运行测试非常重要
It's really important to rerun your test
每当你改变你的代码。
whenever you change your code.
这就是回归的概念。
And this is where the idea of regression comes in.
回归意味着您引入了一个bug
A regression means that you've introduced a bug
你曾经拥有的，你曾经确定的
that you used to have and that you fixed once upon a time
无论何时进行更改或添加新功能。
whenever you make a change or add a new feature.
回归测试，回归测试的概念
So regression testing, the idea of regression testing
是用你的测试来防止自己倒退。
is using your tests to prevent yourself from regressing.
所以每次更改后都要运行所有测试
So run all your tests after every change
为了抓住这些倒退并解决它们。
in order to catch those regressions and fix them.
现在我们如何进行回归测试？
Now how do we do regression testing?
如何确保我们的测试套件
How do we make sure that our test suite is
对回归测试有用吗？
useful for regression testing?
首先我们要选择好的测试用例
Well first of all we want to select good test cases
从规范开始使用分区
from the spec in the first place using the partitioning
边界技术我们已经
and boundary techniques we've already
在这篇文章里讨论过。
talked about in this reading.
但是第二，每当我们发现一个虫子我们想做什么
But second, whenever we find a bug what we want to do
就是输入一个引起那个bug的
is take an input that elicits that bug that
使程序失败，根据那个错误，
makes the program fail, according to that bug,
并将其添加到我们的测试套件中。
and add it to our test suite.
所以我们实际上增加了测试
So we're actually increasing the tests
当我们在软件生命周期中开发代码时。
as we develop the code over the lifetime of the software.
所以一个因为错误而添加的测试用例
So a test case that has been added because of a bug
称为回归测试。
is called a regression test.
它的目的是能够找到
And the purpose of it is to be able to find
如果它再次出现，如果你倒退的话。
that bug if it ever crops up again, if you ever regress.
记住，考试很好
Now remember, a test is good, it's
很好的测试发现了一个错误。
a good test of it finds a bug.
回归测试的奇妙之处
And the wonderful thing about regression tests
他们真的曾经发现过一个虫子，一个虫子
is that they actually did find a bug once upon a time, a bug
你现在已经修好了。
that you've now fixed.
但是通过保存这个测试，你就可以防止逆转。
But by saving that test, you're protecting against reversions.
针对重新引入该错误的代码更改。
Against changes to your code that reintroduce that bug.
这比你想象的要普遍。
And that's more common than you might think.
一个错误很容易犯，
A bug may be a very easy error to make,
因为它已经发生过一次了。
because it already happened once already.
这也引出了先测试后调试的思想。
And this leads us also to the idea of test first debugging.
也就是说，每当你有一个bug，你想做什么
That is, whenever you have a bug, what you want to do
立即为它编写一个测试用例
is immediately write a test case for it
并将该测试用例添加到您的测试套件中。
and add that test case to your test suite.
从那以后你要做什么
And then from then on what you're doing
想让考试通过。
is trying to get that test to pass.
一旦你通过了测试，你就知道你已经修复了这个错误。
Once you get that test to pass you know you've fixed that bug.
但是你也有这个bug的回归测试
But also you have the regression test for that bug
已经在你的测试套件里了。
already in your test suite.
现在在实践中，这两个想法，有了自动化测试
Now in practice these two ideas, having automated testing
使用回归测试防止错误再次出现，
and using regression test to keep bugs from reappearing,
几乎总是组合使用。
are almost always used in combination.
所以用大量的数据做回归测试是非常实用的
So it's really only practical to do regression testing with lots
如果您可以经常运行这些测试
of regression tests if you can run those tests often
而且是自动的。
and automatically.
相反，如果您已经有了自动化测试
And conversely, if you already have automated testing in place
你还是经常跑吧
you might as well run it frequently
防止倒退。
to prevent a regression.
所以自动回归测试真的
So automated regression testing really
是现代软件工程的最佳实践之一。
is one of the best practices of modern software engineering.